I Want to End This Love Game
It broke.
Rematch.
W-We're still doing this?
Why?
Does Miku not feel any way about this?
Come to think of it, I think
Miku moved to break it.
No, she was pretty
surprised right after, too.
She must not have had
any intention of kissing me.
Right?
So then why are we still going?
Because she can't afford to lose?
Because she can't chicken out now?
Miku's definitely acting weird today.
I don't get it.
Episode 10
My Childhood Friend Is Unstoppable
Did that get you?
Something's changing.
It has to be.
I'm sure of it.
I did it. It happened.
Miku and I kissed.
There's no way that doesn't
mean she likes me, right?
But...
something was clearly off.
Love Game or not,
she would never do such a thing.
Kanai East Middle School
Grandma...
I kissed Yukiya for the first time.
At first, it caught me by surprise
when our lips touched.
But I worked up the courage
and did it over and over.
And then Yukiya kissed me back.
His face...
His heart was definitely racing.
He was definitely into me, right?
He's thinking about me now, right?
Yukiya never did it.
Yet I kissed him.
I already knew.
It's cute.
I knew he wasn't saying
that about Akane herself.
But...
Why didn't he say that to me?
I want it.
No!
Don't do it!
I want it now.
I suck.
Why am I so not cute?
I Want to End This Love Game
Aoharu Detectives
Let's all play dodgeball!
I'm in!
Same!
What about you, Sakura-san?
E-Er...
I'm happy they asked,
but I'm bad at dodgeball.
I'm just going to make it
boring for everyone.
I-I'll pass.
Ah...
Okay. Sorry.
Let's just go.
Aoharu Detectives
Sakura-san never joins. It's okay.
Sakura.
Asagi-kun.
Sorry. Thanks.
There we go.
Sakura-san.
You should at least
carry the bucket yourself.
Everyone does it by themselves.
S-Sorry.
Don't cry, Miku-chan.
As long as you're smiling,
I can depart worry-free.
Then I'm going to keep crying!
I'm going to keep worrying!
Please stay here!
Grandma, don't go, or I'll..
I'm going to trouble Grandma again.
Asagi brought a girl with him!
So what? She's my friend.
You have Mihashi and them with you too.
We were gaming when they came here.
Asagi-kun, it's okay.
I don't have any games.
It's fine.
Okay, since there's a lot of us,
how about we play tag?
Sounds good.
You're it then, since you joined last.
I'm it too, then, since I came last.
What?
That's not fair, having two its.
Oh, shut up.
Here we go.
One, two, three, four...
Seriously?!
Oh crap, run!
Sakura, let's hit them from two sides!
O-Okay!
Surround them!
Okay!
Are you okay?
Totally fine.
Hurry up!
Hold it!
Th-They keep getting away.
You guys are both so slow.
I'm starting to feel bad.
You're all so fast.
What are you laughing for?
You're weird.
I'm just having so much fun
playing with all of you.
Sakura-san, wanna hang out
again tomorrow?
But...
Wouldn't I be a nuisance?
Why?
Don't worry about it.
Let's play.
Okay!
Bye!
See you!
Good for you. You made some friends.
Y-Yeah. Thanks.
I've been thinking...
You're cute when you smile.
I wanted him to say more.
I have to change.
So that I can stay by Asagi-kun forever.
What defines a cute girl?
A hardworking girl
A polite girl
A compassionate girl
A cheerful girl
A determined girl
A smiling girl
And yet...
Now I'm not cute at all.
I let my need for approval
get the better of me
and tried to seduce him with a kiss.
I'm so low.
I'm so low, and yet...
it made me happy.
I couldn't help but be happy.
I'm not cute.
I'm not cute. I'm not cute.
I'm really not cute.
Of course he'd never call me cute.
I want Yukiya to stay with me.
I have to become cute.
You're cute when you smile.
Café
It's Yukki!
Yeah.
Hey, it's past closing, isn't it?
I should get going.
It's fine.
Hinako needs to rant. Let her talk.
Exactly.
This cake is on me.
Thank you.
So hear me out, Yukki.
I failed my audition again yesterday.
For that web anime voice part?
Yeah, that.
It was a huge opportunity,
so I practiced so hard.
It's a tough world, huh?
I like your voice too,
and I'm not being biased.
Thank you, Yukki!
Give me sympathy.
Want two different colors
of Puchimon, then?
They're pretty rare.
Ooh.
I'm good.
Hey...
Actually, I have
something on my mind, too.
What is it?
I can't figure out what Miku's thinking.
She just did something
totally out of character.
And she had a serious look on her face.
I messed up, too.
But what she's doing
is so inconsistent...
That kiss must have been an accident.
She must not have wanted that, right?
She must have wanted me to stop her.
But there's no way I could have
stopped after what she did to me.
No...
I knew something was up with Miku.
It was my fault for playing along.
I keep making excuses.
I'm so lame.
What should I have done?
What does Miku want right now?
What's correct?
I have so much to think about.
Setting aside what's correct,
what is it that you want?
I want to hear what Miku has to say.
Puberty's a time of mixed emotions,
especially for girls.
Like that mille-feuille there.
You have trouble even expressing
all the overflowing emotions.
Sometimes they become too much,
and you get crushed.
So give her time and be by her side
until she can sort through her feelings.
Come on, the ice cream is going to melt.
Right.
Thanks.
Onii!
Where'd my gym uniform go?
You didn't take out the laundry!
I put it in the dryer!
I'm heading out, now.
What? You're leaving already?
Okay.
Maybe she already left?
Miku
Miku...
Disconnected
What's wrong, Miku?
\
Are you home right now?
Hey!
Disconnected
What's wrong, Miku?
Are you home right now?
Hey!
Miku
Today
H-Hey...
Asagi-kun?!
What's wrong? You never talk to me!
Yeah, no, yeah, I mean...
Do you know what Miku's up to today?
She said this morning that
she's staying home with a fever.
D-Did she?
She never told you?
She hasn't.
She isn't responding to my calls either.
Why would she ever miss your calls?
Ohagi
I'm... gone.
Has something happened to Miku?!
Ohagi
No, I don't think it's
anything like that.
Miku
Call Connected
Speaker
On
Mute
Nacchan? What's up?
M-M-Miku!
Are you okay? Are you alive?
Should I call an ambulance?
I should! I'm doing it!
Wait, wait.
What's wrong? What's going on?
I'm fine, I'm fine.
I just have a bit of a fever.
I'll be back at school tomorrow.
Oh, thank goodness, what a relief.
Asagi-kun was so worried
about you that he talked to me!
He never does that!
O-Oh, okay.
Sorry.
Tell him I'm okay.
Got it. Take care.
Asagi-kun, Miku's safe.
Asagi-kun?!
What does she mean, she's okay?
Her voice...
That's her voice after
she's been crying!
I...
I made her cry!
To Be Continued
Next Time
My Childhood Friend Embraces Me
Onii's running!
Next episode of I Want to End This Love
Game: "My Childhood Friend Embraces Me."
Run! Run, Onii!